<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sustainability Side Quests</string>

    <string name="main_page_1">Recycle and learn about sustainability to earn points! exchange your points for in-game currency of your favorite games. Don’t miss out on these free rewards!</string>
    <string name="main_page_2">Use our AI while taking photos of your\nday-to-day recycling to earn points!</string>
    <string name="main_page_3">Learn about different ways\nsustainability affects you to earn points!</string>
    <string name="main_page_4">Talk to our AI Chatbot about\nsustainability and inequality!</string>
    <string name="main_page_5">Spend your points to earn in-game\ncurrency for your favorite video games!</string>

    <string name="recycle_name">Recycle Rush</string>
    <string name="recycle_1">As you recycle, take photos of each item to earn points! If the AI detects that it is recycling, then the points get added to your total. The more you recycle, the more points you can earn!</string>

    <string name="quest_log_name">Quest Log</string>
    <string name="quest_log_1">Learn about the different aspects of sustainability and inequality and how they affect each other. Each quest rewards you with 100 points!</string>
    <string name="quest_log_2">What is Sustainability?</string>
    <string name="quest_log_3">Trash VS Recycling</string>
    <string name="quest_log_4">Different Types of Plastic</string>
    <string name="quest_log_5">Why Recycle?</string>
    <string name="quest_log_6">Landfills and Pollution</string>
    <string name="quest_log_7">Minorities and Sustainability</string>
    <string name="quest_log_8">Gender Ratio in Waste Management</string>

    <string name="rewards_name">Rewards</string>
    <string name="rewards_1">Time to use those points! We’ve partnered with the following games to help create a more sustainable future. Choose a game and log into your account to transfer your points. All conversion rates are based on the value of a $20 gift card.</string>

    <string name="bot_name">Sust.AI.nability</string>
    <string name="bot_1">Talk to our AI Chatbot for 10m to earn 100 points! You can chat about anything related to sustainability and inequality and how they affect each other.</string>
    <string name="bot_2">(Did not earn chat points yet for this week)</string>
    <string name="bot_3">Hello! I am your sust.AI.nability chat bot! What would you like to talk about today?</string>
    <string name="bot_4">That\'s a great thought! Unfortunately my chat function isn\'t working yet, but I can\'t wait to have a conversation with you!</string>

</resources>